Heart of Glass
Once I had a love and it was a gas
Soon turned out had a heart of glass
Seemed like the real thing only to find
Mucho mistrust love's gone behind
Once I had a love and it was divine
Soon found out
I was losing my mind
It seemed like the real thing but
I was so blind
Mucho mistrust love's gone behind
In between what
I find is pleasing and
I'm feeling fine
Love is so confusing there's no peace of mind
If I fear
I'm losing you it's just no good
You teasing like you do
Once I had a love and it was a gas
Soon turned out had a heart of glass
Seemed like the real thing only to find
Mucho mistrust love's gone behind
Lost inside adorable illusion and
I cannot hide
I'm the one you're using please don't push me aside
We could have made it cruising yeah
Na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na
Yeah riding high on love's true bluish light
Ooh oh, ooh oh
Once I had a love and it was a gas
Soon turned out had a heart of glass
Seemed like the real thing only to find
Mucho mistrust love's gone behind
In between what
I find is pleasing and
I'm feeling fine
Love is so confusing there's no peace of mind
If I fear
I'm losing you it's just no good
You teasing like you do
Na na na
Na na na na na na na na na